When you two marshmallows first stepped up to the mat,
I was like "breakdancing is gonna roast them alive."
(Both scoff)
But I've been spitting a little knowledge to you two,
and you all have soaked it up.
Mix master Maddie in the house!
Joey: Yeah.
Maddie, what are you doing here?
Diggie, I realized that...
Being a part of a couple
means sometimes doing things that the other person likes.
So I met up with q-pop earlier, and he taught me a couple moves.
I figure if I can't beat 'em, break 'em.
Oh, and if you can't break 'em, breakdance.
(Mouthing)
Seriously, Maddie, breakdancing is mc j-town and dig-dog's thing... whoa!
(Clears throat)
Cue it, pop.
Oh, that's how I do!
(Dance music playing)
And that is how I do.
Yeah, okay. Beat it, Joey.
(Beatboxing)
The other "beat it."
I know.