(Both growl, sniff)
Great training sesh this morning, fangs.
It was so much fun chasing ducks.
Tell me about it.
They've had it too good for too long.
I think we've earned lunch.
(Both growl)
(Gasps) Eating off the floor.
Were you raised by wolves?
Mom.
Oh, sorry sorry.
Sorry sorry sorry.
Thanks for training with me so hard this week, fangs.
I am going to nail this audition.
That part is so mine, am I right?
(Growls)
When the wolf is silent, the wolf disapproves.
What's wrong?
As good as you're doing, the only way you're gonna nail that audition
is if you nail your howl.
It is the heart and soul of any wolf.
(Howls)
(Dogs barking) Wow, I...
Think you scared every dog in the neighborhood.
No.
There's a doberman on the next block who didn't reply.
(Howls)
(Dog barks)
There he is.
He apologized.
You can't pee and bark at the same time.
Okay, Rooney. Your turn.
Okay.
(Growls)
(Howls)
(Vocalizes "Amazing Grace")
Quit goofing around.
You're not taking your howl seriously.
You know what?
I'm out.
What?
You can't be out. We're in a pack.
You licked my face.
I'm sorry, Rooney.
We've gone as far as we can go.
Plus, I'm itchy and your mom won't let me drag my butt on your carpet.
You know what? Fine.
I am going to be an awesome Tristan without your help.
Oh, you want this?
Mmm. Yeah?
Yeah, I know you want it.
Yum yum, right?
Go get it!
(Panting)
(Sighs) Stupid wolf.