Whoa.
(Dance music stops) That was awesome, qpop.
Yeah, q-pop don't stop.
Oh.
(Beats)
Mc j-town in da house.
Mc j-town be his own boy.
Respect!
Joey, this is q-pop.
He's our dance instructor.
Oh, well, it's a pleasure to meet you, Mr. pop.
My mission is to get fresh, stay fresh, then refresh.
I just dropped my motto on this grotto.
(Grunts)
This is so cool.
I can't believe Maddie bailed.
I feel so alive.
Her loss is the breaking bros' gain.
Plus, who knew I lived in a grotto.
Right?
All right. Let's see what y'all are working with.
Time to get fresh, y'all.
When I drop the beat, I want to see you robot.
(Dance music playing)
Oh... no.
Gentlemen, are y'all trying to make q-pop cry?
All right, let's try to back it up to a simpler move, okay?
This one is called "finding the beat!"
(Snaps fingers)
Okay, wait. Slow down.
How are you making that noise with your fingers?