(Whimpers)
Yes, yes, no, book it, hate it, orange... Who is this?!
- Liv Rooney, superstar. - Hi.
Been dying to meet the girl who's got the nerve
to go up against Ryan Gosling and Vin diesel.
We are dying to see what you have for us today.
(Bell rings)
Now remember, the most important thing
is that big howl at the end of your speech.
Really let loose.
Take all the time you need to get ready.
I don't want to rush you.
And action!
This was it.
This was my chance to become a movie star.
By the sting of my proton whip, I will bring you to your knees,
for I am your doom.
I am wolf.
I am Tristan Lycanth.
And?!
Oh, right. And scene. (Giggles)
No, where was my howl?
I need to hear a howl.
Let's try it again from the top.
Okay. (Clears throat)
Um, just to be clear, though, this is gonna be without the howl?
With the howl.
Right.