Ready?
Rye bread, marmalade, pureed cauliflower, the good bologna
and just a hint of toenail.
Left foot, big toe.
(Laughs)
Nailed it.
Okay. So boys, you got me a little bit nervous
about my "space werewolves" audition,
so I decided to get my wolf on with this:
"The way of the wolf" by emmy "fangs" wolfert.
"Fangs" is a teenage wolf girl.
When she was little, she wandered off on a camping trip
and spent the ne 10 years of her life in the wild being raised by wolves.
(Chuckles)
I wonder if that's how Maddie became Maddie.
(Laughs)
She likes wolves. Big whoop.
I heard diesel wants thpart so bad, he had wolf fangs surgically implanted.
What?
And for the past two months, Gosling's been eating nothing but roadkill.
(Stammers)
They're gonna crush me.
Okay, I need your help.
How do I figure out Tristan? What's his thing?
No brainer. It's his howl.
Okay, yeah. I got this.
(Clears throat)
(Howls, scats)
It's like 50% wolf, 50% Liv.
What do you guys think?
- Diesel. - Gosling.