(Mouthing)
Okay.
Get ready for a howl that is going to change your life.
(Chuckles) Okay, get ready.
It's coming. (Clears throat)
Although, you know...
Just sort of like off the top of my head,
what if it was sort of less of a howl and more of a whistle?
Yeah, yeah.
'Cause I mean, the audience totally...
just howl!
Got it.
(Howls)
My name is fangs wolfert, and I'm here to try out for the part of Tristan.
What are you doing?
(Chuckles)
Just give me one second to talk to my wolf coach real quick.
Get out.
A wolf takes what it wants.
And I'm taking this part.
Oh.
We are on a soundstage right now, fangs.
This is my territory.
Doesn't look like it.
(Growls)
I am Tristan Lycanth.
No, I am Tristan Lycanth.
(Howls powerfully)
(Dogs barking)
And scene.
Wow.
Let us discuss and we'll get back to you.
Find out who styles the brunette's hair.
I love it.
Fangs!
All part of my plan.
(Chuckles)
Oh-ho...
You are good.
I knew that if I threatened your territory, all our hard work would pay off
and your inner wolf would emerge.
Well, I don't know if I'd beat Gosling or diesel,
but I did it, fangs. I howled.
I heard.
It sounded like my mother.
(Both howl)