Okay, here we go.
Okay, this is just frozen mustard.
But from where?
A light yellow dijon originally crafted in France
but now manufactured in Kentucky...
Dipped once...
no.
Twice!
In hot dog water.
Ah.
Inspiring.
(Doorbell rings)
Fangs is here! Fangs is here.
Ooh, the girl from the book?
Yeah. You guys were right.
I've realized that if I want this part I have to do something really big,
so I hired fangs to help me tap into my inner wolf.
Delivery for Liv Rooney?
- Sign here. - Okay.
Oh.
That's so weird. Maybe fangs had all her bags shipped here?
(Chuckles)
(Growls)
Is that fangs?
No, munch, it's a different girl who was raised by wolves.
Hello, fangs!
Me Liv!
(Sniffs)
I read this in her book.
She has to get used to the smell of new people.
Your scent is acceptable.
(Sighs)
Sorry about the cage.
My wolf instincts are strong, and I don't trust myself around new humans.
Plus, it's cheaper to travel in cargo.
Well, fangs, these are my brothers.
(Yelps)
(Sniffs)
(Squeals)
Not gonna lie, I'm into this.
Glad you called, Rooney.
I never miss a chance to make sure wolves
are accurately portrayed in the media.
Well, then, if anyone asks, I will proudly state for the record
that you did not eat my grandma or blow my house down. (Chuckles)
See, that right there?
Offensive.
Let's begin.
Tristan Lycanth is half-wolf.
Wolves are majestic, fierce creatures.
You got any wolf in you, Rooney?
Um, no. No, she does not.
Live she sniffed my pits.
I can't lie to her.
Howl for me.
It's the most important part about being a wolf.
It asserts your dominance.
Well, my howl is dom-alicious.
(Growls)
(Howls, vocalizes)
Rooney, we have work to do.
What?
You're gonna live like a wolf, hunt like a wolf, eat like a wolf
and poop like a wolf.
Oh, I can show her the last one.
Yeah, I can imitate the pooping styles of 84 different animal species.
Your offer of a poop demo is appreciated, little man.
But Liv's my student now.
Welcome to my wolf pack.
(Gasps)
This is gonna be so awesome.