Okay. Take a sip.
You will never guess what's in this one.
Skim milk, avocado, peanut butter, a hint of zit puss,
celery juice and half a chewed-up chicken nugget.
I have said it before, and I will say it again.
Amazing.
Boys boys boys boys boys boys.
(Squeals)
Set your phasers to excitement.
Okay.
The producers of "space werewolves" just called.
There are apparently only three actors still in the running for the lead,
and I'm one of them!
Both: Whoo!
(All shout)
"Space werewolves"
is the greatest Sci-Fi graphic novel ever.
It is the epic tale of Tristan Lycanth, half-wolf, half-human,
and his battle to save his planet.
It is like "star wars" and "lord of t rings" had a baby,
and then "the avengers" adopted it.
Tristan is the baddest dude in the galaxy.
But if Liv gets the part, they're gonna change him to a her.
And then the baddest dude in the galaxy
will be...
My sister.
Guys, my final audition is in a week.
This is the part that could make me a movie star.
Unbelievable.
My sister is gonna be Tristan Lycanth.
Who are the two losers you're up against?
Ryan Gosling and Vin Diesel.
Both: Ohh!