- Hey. - Hey. You keep saying
you want to do couple-y things
now that we're officially in like?
Well, it's mostly been you that's been saying that,
but you're really cute when you talk, so continue.
Well, I signed us up for dance lessons.
Ooh.
That could be romantic.
What kind? Saa, tango, waltz?
Breakdanng!
(Laughs)
(Snorts) Breakdancing?
- Yeah. - (Chuckles)
Um, Diggie, that's not couple-y.
Oh, mads, you're so wrong.
My wave could connect right to your wave.
What!
Ah, chain wave.
Give me some of that.
(Whooshing)
Sorry, guys. Breaking's just not really my thing.
It's hard to believe we're even related.
Um, well... hey, here's an idea.
You guys both seem really excited about this,
so why don't you take the lessons together?
And then Diggie, you and I can figure out something that we both want to do.
We are breaking bros now.
Chain wave.
(Both whooshing)
Yeah yeah, that was nice.
Now let me show you my wave.
Buh-bye.