And if you need the restroom, it's just back that way.
Nah.
Marked my territory on your porch before I came in.
Ooh, got an itch.
Can't get it. Can't get it.
- Can't get it. - Okay.
Help a wolf out!
Oh!
(Murmurs) (Chuckles)
Ahh, that's the stuff.
Yeah?
Wolf girl is cray cray.
But she is going to give me the forest cred
that I need to really nail this audition.
(Chuckles) Scrape that off the road and eat it, Gosling.
This is from the forest where my wolf family raised me.
Lots of good stink to roll around in.
Oh!
Ah.
(Gasps)
Ahh.
Your turn, wolf pup.
Get up in it.
(Clears throat) Okay.
(Chuckles)
Whoo.
Look at me.
Scooting around in the filth.
Whoo.
Like an animal.
I am wild!
- Rooney... - Yeah?
- Can I get real for a minute? - Mm-hmm?
If you want to ace this audition, you have to go full wolf.
Wolves are territorial animals.
- Yeah. - They take what's theirs,
and they don't back down. - Yeah.
Let's try something else.
What?
You want it?
Take it.
- Okay. - (Growls)
(Gasps)
(Growls)
(Sighs)
(Both growling)
I'm gonna go get the hose.