Okay, Liv and Maddie will be back from their driving test any second.
Ready to celebrate?
Check it.
Sing it loud!
Bam! What?!
Ooh, I can't wait to get my license
and be able to go wherever I want.
( Laughs ) Within the city limits.
Before my curfew.
In a beat-up minivan that smells like Joey's feet.
Still freedom.
Whoo-hoo!
Freedom?
( Scoffs ) Try loss of freedom.
Who wants to drive when you can sit shotgun
and text until your thumbs fall off?
( Chuckles ) Not me.
I'm stoked for Maddie. Having a license...
that means she can go anywhere and do anything.
That a responsible teenager would do
after getting approval from her father.
Not that I've ever asked her not to get approval.
Why am I still talking?
( Mouthing )
Why are you in my house?
Why haven't you gotten a haircut?
We've all got questions.
( Gasps ) There she is.
- ( All cheer ) - Congratulations, Liv.
One of our two new drivers.
Yes. Hold your rah-rahs.
Only one of us passed.
Total bummer-rang.
Aw, you'll get it next time, kid.
No. I'm the one who passed.
( Laughs ) License to surprise!
Wait, if you passed, that means Maddie failed.
Maddie doesn't fail anything.
- Ooh! - Oh!
( Shouts )
Burn it! Burn it all!
( All chatter )
Well...
I failed.
Guess I know what it feels like to be a loser now.
You know what I'm talking about, Joey.
Ouch! I would call that a drive-by...
if you had your license.
( Imitates explosion )
So what happened?
I will tell you what happened.
The DMV discriminates.
Yeah. They only give their licenses
to people who can make left-hand turns.
They do come in handy when you want to go left.
Why would you purposefully turn
into oncoming traffic when you can go up one block
and make three rights?
Who needs their license anyway, am I right?
I do! I need my license!
Don't worry, Maddie. I'll drive you anywhere you want to go.
Seriously, why am I still talking?
Why am I still here?
I'll go get my hair cut.