Okay, we are good to go.
Uh, I think we're forgetting one thing.
Oh! Ha ha. Yes.
Lip gloss.
No, it says here you're required to wear glasses
to drive.
( Laughs )
Does it say that?
I thought I just needed those for the picture.
( Both laugh )
Put 'em on.
O. M. Eyeballs.
Now start the car and put it in gear.
Absolutely. ( Laughs )
If you could just... Direct me to the...
Ignition.
( Laughing )
No?
( Starts ignition )
All right. This is good.
Now merge left. There's construction ahead.
- Uh... - Go left. I said left!
- ( Tires squeal ) - ( Screams )
Okay, too far, too far.
- Okay. - Garbage can.
- I don't... - ( Tires squealing )
- ( Shouts ) - ( Thuds )
( Horn blares )
Okay.
Pull the vehicle over.
Uh, uh, okay.
Slow down. Slow down!
- I'm not... I... - Mailbox.
- Mailbox! - What?!
- ( Thuds ) - ( Both scream )
( Airbags hiss )
So... ( Sighs )
Pass?