Ugh!
323 pages
of "Rules of the Road,"
and not once did they admit
that turning left into oncoming traffic
is insane.
420 pages of werewolves and spaceships,
and the only thing I'm really looking is that
I think I could totally rock Tristan's space suit.
Yeah...
just wait till they get to the Battle of Mirth.
( Imitates gunfire )
That's when he meets Kytra,
and that's when the adventure really kicks off.
( Gasps )
You undercover Sci-Fi geek.
You've totally read this book.
Yeah, I've actually read them all.
I love them. And I have to admit...
I am a little on the fence about you playing Tristan myself.
Okay... one, how dare you.
And two, help me.
Okay, Liv, why are you wigging out?
Because I really want this role.
I mean, I know that I've been playing it cool,
but this is way bigger than my show
and it could send me into a completely new acting stratosphere.
I just have no idea how to impress these fanboys.
Okay, well, I would love to help you
but, Liv, my driver's test is on the same day
as your autograph signing.
And I still have no idea
how to make a stupid left-hand turn.
I have a twin-sane idea!
This Saturday, I'll be you and you be me.
- Wait, you mean like... - A switch-a-Rooney.
( Both scream )
I'll face your fanboys.
And I will take your driver's test.
Perfect! ( Laughs )
Why is this bed so squishy?
( Clears throat )
Because I am sitting on a pizza.
A girl gets hungry at 3:00 A.M.