Final question, girl.
When Tristan split the galactic pangaea,
what did he say to the scattering colonies?
"Run to the stars, wolves.
- ( Mouthing along ) - But always put first your families.
For their love
keeps you tethered to the universe."
( Sighs ) Wow. You've gotta admit...
Maddie's making Liv look really good.
She's not fooling anyone.
Well, except everyone here.
Well, Liv Rooney...
I'm sold.
I mean, you will make a great Tristan Lycanth.
All hail the she-Tristan!
( Howling loudly )
And, FYI...
I currently am available for le prom.
( Chuckles, roars )
But your window of opportunity
is closing.
Boop!
Artie.
Are you serious?
You can accept my sister playing Tristan?
What part of... ( Howls loudly )
Don't you understand?
Okay, so Parker and I are the only ones
that have a problem with this?
Um, speak for yourself.
She won me over too.
Artie, tail me.
( Singing stately tune )
( Howls )
( Howling )
It was at that moment that I realized
I was the crazy fanboy
that I was trying to protect Liv from.
I was untethered from my family.
I was the lone wolf.
And I should not have eaten 15 gummy eyeballs.
You know what, Artie...
tail me too.
All hail the she-Tristan!