Guys! I have something really exciting to say.
How about you pause your piehole for two hours?
We'll get to you later.
We're all listening, Liv.
Okay.
There is a major film
shooting in Wisconsin this summer,
and I'm up for a big part.
How exciting! What's it about?
It's based on some book about wolves in space.
Both: "Space Werewolves!"
( Squeals ) That is my favorite graphic novel.
No way!
They want me to play Tristan.
As in Tristan Lycanth?
Yeah.
The hero?
Ha ha, but Tristan's a boy.
Technically half-boy, half-werewolf.
But he is definitely not a girl.
Right. Not yet.
But the people making the movie saw my episode of Sing it  Loud!
right where I dreamt that I was on an international space station
and I saved the earth by singing the high note
that shattered the asteroid before it hit earth. Aah!
( Sings high note )
( Imitates explosion )
I love that episode.
Really? 'Cause I had some logic problems with it.
But you sparkled, honey.
They liked it so much that they're considering changing the role of Tristan
into a girl just for me.
I had to stop Liv for her own good.
Fanboys are crazy.
I should know. I'm one of them.
( Clicks tongue )
We're talking about Tristan Lycanth.
Keeper of the claw of freedom.
Does this match this?