Here we are... a couple of dudes
getting ready to do some chillin' and grillin'.
Are you okay that I just called you a dude?
Relax, we're barbecuing.
Everybody's a dude.
Okay. Let's do this.
Absolutely.
First, I need you to do a few things.
Hit me. Whatever you want.
Shuck the corn? Season the meat?
Mow the lawn.
Um, what?
And clean the gutters, rotate my tires,
grout the tub, and empty the dishwasher.
Dude.
What does that have to do with barbecuing?
I thought you came here to learn.
Let me go get the lawn mower.
( Door opens )
I knew exactly what Diggie was doing.
Using barbecue to soften up the old man?
If he wanted to get on my good side,
he was going to have to get on the good side
of my to-do list.
Finally, a little thrilla on the grilla!
All those chores made me hungry.
( Snaps )
That's mine.
What... did you forget to bring your own steak?
Maybe next time.
Next time?
I'm in! ( Laughs )
- ( Sizzles ) - Aah!
"Bring your own steak." Classic!
Why are you messing with that poor boy?
I'm just making sure he's good enough for my daughter.
And I'm done for the day.
Don't tell Maddie,
but except for that stupid name,
Diggie's all right.