- What's up, Diggie? - What's up, Rooney?
'Sup with your hair?
You did not get a haircut
just because my dad told you to.
( Scoffs ) No. Not at all.
I totally needed a trim. Do you think he'll like it?
Diggie, you can't let him push you around like this.
I mean, your hair was a hot mess,
but that's not the point.
I can't help it, okay? I want him to like me.
He's your dad. And you and me are...
Whatever we are.
Totally. Whatever.
Um... you just need to find something
that you and my dad both like and bond over that.
Oh, yeah, okay, great. Let's see.
He likes growling at me.
You know what else he likes...
barbecuing.
Grilling sure beats growling.
And, if he starts to like me,
I could help you prep for your driver's test.
Aww. ( Laughs, snorts )
That's so sweet.
- Hey, Dad. - ( Exclaims )
( Laughs )
Dude, I'm kidding. Ha ha.
But he won't be.