Let me make one thing clear.
This was the last switch-a-Rooney.
You did it when you were 6.
And I wrote your names on your forehead
in permanent marker.
Don't make me do that again.
Ah, yes... the summer of headbands.
To be fair, though, we rocked the headband look.
( Laughs )
Ha ha fun fun.
Maddie, no license till you're 17.
Rock that look.
17?! Seriously?
You want to make it 18?
Ah, 17. Looking forward to it.
And Liv,
since you like driving so much,
you are now my personal chauffeur until further notice.
- No! - ( Laughing ) Yes.
There is no errand too small, no trip too far.
I might even have you take me down to the end of the driveway
just to get the newspaper.
I don't know.
That's right, girls.
I just dropped an atomic mom bomb.
Boom!
She can't be serious about that, right?
Do we seriously still get newspapers
delivered to our house?
Hey, whatever you did down at Neville's totally worked.
Some fanboy named lone wolf started a petition
to get me the role of Tristan.
You won over the fanboys.
Thank you.
Pretty sure lone wolf is actually lone Joey.
You should go thank him.
Wait, I thought you said that Joey
was the one trying to sabotage us.
It was a long and complicated day.
Got it.
Also I'm sorry about wrecking your driver's test.
Literally. Ha!
And I got you something.
You might want to return this to the... hoovers.
Thanks.
That reminds me.
I got you something as well.
One of Artie's wolf tails. Yeah.
Oh! Also I got you a date to the prom.
( Laughs ) Yeah.
Artie would like to know what kind of dress
you will be wearing... Wizard or Pegasus?