Hey, check it out...
I sold Liv's toothbrush to a "Sing it Loud!" Fan
and got us a bunch of gummy eyeballs.
( Mouths )
Too bad she only has one toothbrush.
Oh, please... I picked that one off the sidewalk out front.
Oh...
The switch-a-Rooney was on.
It took me four hours to do my hair
and Liv made me sleep with my head hanging off the mattress
to protect the pouf.
( Snorts )
I drooled into my own nose.
( Cheering )
( Scattered applause )
( Object shatters )
Thank you all so much for coming
to the season 4 DVD signing
of  Sing it Loud!
Artie's here.
Let the games begin.
Liv Rooney.
Are the rumors true that you,
a girl, might play Tristan Lycanth?
( Clicks, drops pen )
It's true, fanboy.
What say you?
I say it's intergalactic blasphemy!
And I shall prove you're unworthy.
Be warned my minions are live blogging.
King_Artie_the_magnificent @ wolfspot dot howl.
Ha ha.
Bring it on, king Artie.
Speak for Tristan's lineage.
Who are his parents?
Liv is about to go down in flames.
His parents
are the werewolf Magrol
and queen Zira.
Bam! What?!
( Laughs )
I mean, space-tastic question.
Both: Maddie.