Web... and that's how I slay the dragon.
Hey, Artie, you got a minute?
Hey, Joey.
You got a girlfriend?
Burn!
How is that a burn? You took your mom to the freshman dance last fall.
So, what brings you crawling back
to the Society of Space... Space... space...
Were... were... were... Wol... wol... wol...
wol... wol... wol... ves... ves?
( Howls )
I was voted out of the Society
for suggesting that wolf tails were stupid.
Was I wrong?
People, was I wrong?
I want to talk to you about my sister Liv.
No la la la la.
We do not speak the name of that she-devil
who wants to desecrate Tristan.
Unless she sent you to ask me to prom,
in which case, let her know I say maybe.
Be gone with you.
( Yelps )
Listen, Artie.
We have a common enemy here,
and we need to work together
to defend the iconic character
that is Tristan.
We were once powerful allies, you and I.
An uneasy alliance.
My wolf ears are perked.
Liv will be down at Neville's tomorrow.
I need you to show her the real fangs
of a true "Space Werewolves" fanboy.
Fanboy?
That term is derogatory, sir.
We prefer "fantasy enthusiast."
So will you do it?
Oh, sounds great, Joey.
I'd happily waltz right into your trap.
Do you take me for a fool?!
Yes. Yes, I do.
But as Tristan himself would say...
( In a deep voice ) When an enemy
- offers his paw, lick it. - ( Mouthing along )
If only to tear off his hind leg...
Tomorrow.
Oh!
Saying no to that would be like
saying no to Tristan himself.
Well played, lone wolf.
Well played indeed.
( Howls loudly )
Aah!
Nerds!