Oh! Hey, Liv, you want some chocolate pudding?
We found a big bowl of it in the fridge.
Um, boys, that's not chocolate pudding.
That's my organic face mask from Paris.
Oh, ho ho ho.
Fancy pudding.
Yeah. It's made with orangutan poop.
( Sputters )
Well, whatever that monkey ate was delicious.
Is that banana?
Okay, just...
Eww, Joey...
( clears throat )
Get this.
Somehow word has spread through the blogosphere
that I'm up for the role of Tristan in "Space Werewolves."
Not sure how that info leaked out onto the Internet.
We would never post that juicy tidbit
on the Stevens Point "Space Werewolves" fan page
in hopes of enraging local Tristanites.
( Laughs )
Liv will thank me for this later.
Let me guess.
The fanboys were none too pleased
about you playing Tristan.
You probably want to throw in the towel
and back out.
Uh, no.
I mean, why do I care what nerd nation
Because we are a powerful force to be reckoned with...
I mean, they are!
( Clears throat ) Whatever.
This weekend I have a personal appearance
at Neville's Novelty Shoppe to sign "Sing it Loud!" DVDs.
Why don't you guys come with me?
Liv, Neville's is fanboy central.
and then find out that you don't know what you're talking about
they will eat you alive.
He's a werewolf and he lives in space.
I think anything else I need to learn about him will be in here.
I can probably finish this by Saturday, yeah?
Liv, that's volume 1.
There are 64 volumes.
Hah!
No wonder they're making this into a movie.
Who would want to read all that?