I don't know when you and Jenny worked out that comedy routine, but it was hysterical.
[Laughs]
No, that wasn't planned. She was trying to destroy me.
[Snorts] Come on, Liv. That sweet little girl was not trying to destroy you.
Did you all not just see the candy cane beat down?
She was doing absolutely everything she could to make me look bad.
Give her a break, Liv.
Do you not remember how you were at her age?
I was not a monster like that.
- I have to go get wardrobe. - Got to work on that tree.
- [Camera shutter clicks] - [Sighs]
Ho ho ho.
So you are the last kid on Santa's lap.
What are you gonna do?
Pee on me, spit in my face,
pour itching powder down my suit, throw my glasses in the bushes?
I have seen it all today, kid.
Just pick one and do it quick.
[Blows]
Blowing your nose in my beard was not an option.
Get off of me.
[Groans]
Parker, there you are.
Here's 10 bucks. Add it to the pot. How much did we end up with?
Including the 10 bucks, that would be... [mouths]
10 bucks.
What? They've been handing you money all afternoon. Where did it go?
I'm sorry. I meant 10 bucks and this.
[Helicopter whirs]
One Screaming Dragon helicopter.
You used all of our Santa money and bought yourself the helicopter?
I also paid kids to pee on you, spit in your face,
pour itching powder down your suit, and throw your glasses into the bushes.
Why?
Because Mom was gonna get that helicopter for me until you wrecked my dream.
Welcome to Christmas revenge.
Ho-ho-how you like me now?
The only reason I did this Santa stand was so I could pay off your Christmas present.
[Grunts]
I talked Mom out of getting you that helicopter...
Because I already got it for you.
I'm sorry, munch. I had no idea you cared.
Me either. I guess it's just the Christmas spirit.
Come on.
Are you hugging me because you love me, or because you're covered in kid pee?
Mm, why can't it be both?