Ho ho ho.
No no no.
Dude, what's with the suit?
I have a plan to turn Christmas cheer into Christmas ka-ching.
Ka-ching just bought you 15 seconds.
Impress me.
Okay, so they do that holiday spectacular tree lighting ceremony
in the park next to Ridgewood High.
But do you know what they don't have?
Seven more seconds to impress me?
A Santa stand.
Adorable kids plus sentimental parents equals cold hard cash.
Whoa. You actually had a good idea.
It's a Christmas miracle.
Well I spent too much on Christmas presents this year and I owe Dad some money.
I need your help. So...
You in?
Keep your friends close and your jerky brother closer.
If I can't play with the helicopter until I break it,
I'm gonna play with Joey until I break him.
A little quality time with my big bro on Christmas Eve?
- You bet. - [Chuckles]