Ho ho ho, who wouldn't go?
Up on the housetop click click click.
Down through the chimney with good Saint Nick.
[Squeals]
Jenny, that was so great.
That means everything coming from you, Liv.
Well between this duet and Liv's solo,
this is going to be the best tree lighting ceremony ever.
Oh, thank you, Mrs. Rooney, for your wonderful flute playing.
It's like listening to beauty share a hug with Grace.
Well, thank you, Jenny.
You know, I was a bit of a triple threat in high school myself.
Flute, baton twirling, and flag spinning.
Pep squad in the house.
Once you've mastered the flag twirl...
You never forget.
It's in my bones.
Well, I'm gonna go check on dinner.
Now you girls keep practicing. You sound great.
Aw. Everyone sounds great when they're singing with Liv.
[Giggles]
Because you sound like a dying walrus.
[Chuckles]
You are just too sweet.
Wait, what?
Listen up, blondie.
I'm making some changes starting with this stupid outfit.
I'm the star of the show. I should have the cool dress!
Um...
I'm pretty sure I'm the star of the show. I am the one lighting the tree,
oh, and also I'm the one who had her own hit TV show.
If you try to steal my spotlight, I will chew you up and spit you out.
Mrs. Rooney.
Could you drive me home? I promised Mommy I'd read to grandpa tonight.
Well, you are just too good to be true.
Sure, I was just gonna get some things for dinner. Let's go.
Not before I get a hug from Liv.
[Giggles]
Watch your back.