Good...
Evening, Stevens Point!
And...
Welcome to the channel four tree lighting holiday spectacular.
Brought to you by Greenstein's Bagels...
Your schmear for Christmas cheer.
Mmm!
Delicious. Hey, everybody, I'm Johnny Nimbus.
The only weatherman guaranteeing you a white Christmas.
That's right. No other channel's predicting snow.
- Why you gotta hate, channel eight? - [Laughs]
Cue my snow.
- Come on. - [Applause]
Here it comes.
Any minute now. All right, it's coming, folks.
Don't worry about it, but hey, right now, I want you to give it
up for hometown sweetheart Liv Rooney!
And newcomer Jenny Keene.
Up on the housetop reindeer pause.
Out jumps good old Santa Claus.
Down through the chimney with lots of toys.
All for the little ones, Christmas joys.
How dare that ungrateful little reindeer
come out wearing the same cutie claus outfit as me.
And look cuter than me in it.
Ho ho ho, who wouldn't go?
Up on the housetop, click click click.
Down through the chimney with good Saint Nick.
Oops. I think I just landed myself on the naughty list.
Ho ho ho, who wouldn't go?
Up on the housetop, click click click.
Down through the chimney with good Saint Nick.