This is channel four meteorologist Johnny Nimbus!
Coming at you live from the sight of tomorrow's holiday spectacular.
And I'm here alongside Pete Rooney,
the Chairman of the Stevens Point tree lighting committee.
Now, Pete, I see a tree, not a lot of lights.
Don't leave us in the dark. [Laughs]
Classic Nimbus.
But seriously, what have you got planned?
Are we on the air now, like, now now?
Now?
Hi.
Uh, yeah we're live to over 50,000 viewers.
Although I think that number drops every second
you stand there like a frozen snowman.
Excuse me, Johnny. Hi. I'm Maddie Rooney, co-chair.
And think I could shed some light on that.
[Laughs]
Classic Maddie. [Sighs]
So we envision a tree completely lit by candles.
And we call it "Christmas unplugged".
Hmm. "Christmas unplugged".
Well, last year the Griswold family lit their tree with lasers
and then they had a stealth bomber fly over and drop tinsel, but hey...
I guess not everybody has to try.
- So... - Uh, wait.
You didn't let me finish.
We were going to do the thing that I just said, but then we changed our
minds and came up with something bigger and better and more awesome-er.
All right. That's what Stevens Point wants to hear.
Come on, give me the deets. What have you got planned?
Merry Christmas.
Well, Johnny, I think we're trying to keep
our master plan kind of under wraps right now.
But I can promise you that the Rooney tree is going to be
the biggest and the best that Stevens Point has ever seen.
Bam, what?!
Oh-ho!
All right. You heard it from Maddie Rooney.
Boom, zap!
So don't forget to come on down tomorrow night and see this amazing tree!
In the snow!
That's right. Rebel meteorologist Johnny Nimbus is ignoring the mega doppler radar,
and every other station in town to guarantee you!
A white Christmas.
Nimbus out.
- Great job, kid. - Thanks.
[Groans]
What did I just do?
I just promised that we could top the Griswolds' tinsel flyby.
Why did I just promise that?
Next time, just let me do the talking.