Oh, I am so excited that you're headlining channel four's holiday spectacular.
Partly because it's great for the town,
but mostly because I'd already told the committee you'd say yes.
I mean, how can I say no?
This is where it all began eight years ago.
My little baby's first time out on stage singing her little heart out.
I still remember how you wowed the crowd with "Frosty the Snowman".
And "White Christmas".
And "Little Drummer Boy".
By the time you'd finished "O Little Town of Bethlehem,"
I felt like I'd walked there myself.
I never wanted it to end.
And it almost didn't.
Liv Rooney?
Hi. I'm Jenny Keene.
Hi. You are the adorable little girl that I get
to share the stage with this Christmas Eve.
I watched your audition tape, and you have some serious pipes, young lady.
It feels so good to be talented, doesn't it?
I want to be just like you when I grow up.
Well, you are certainly on the right track.
Eight years ago, I was you.
I was a starry-eyed little girl, excited to make her first TV appearance.
[Giggles]
And I mean, after this show, my life changed forever.
It's true. Without it, Liv never would have been cast
in a local commercial as Mandy, the singing muffler.
[Clears throat]
Mandy says your muffler is a-okay.
- [Clicks teeth] - [Chuckles]
We still get a discount.
But I didn't really have anyone to guide me, so I wanted to be that for you.
You know, this industry can get kind of tough, and it's good to have a mentor.
I can't believe Liv Rooney's going to be my celebrity mentor.
Oh, stop. Celebrity mentor?
[Chuckles] You don't have to say that...
I mean, you definitely can. I'm not gonna stop you.