Oh.
That girl is such an Angel. She insisted that I give you these cookies.
[Gasps] Mom! Don't eat those.
Now I know we watch our carbs around the holidays, but what was that?
Jenny Keene is a monster.
Yeah.
One minute it's "beauty sharing a hug with Grace".
And the next it's "watch your back".
Honey, that can't be true.
During the ride home, she sang me "the 12 days of Christmas"...
Complimented my shoes, and offered me gas money.
Ha! She's a liar. Your shoes are hideous.
Honey...
Imagine how scared that little girl must be to share a spotlight with Liv Rooney.
Yeah. [Chuckles] I guess you're right.
Must be so cold there in my shadow.
Look, this is what being a mentor is all about.
That little girl needs your guidance.
I guess everybody gets nervous in different ways.
You know some people chew their fingernails,
and other people turn into a Demon spawn.
Well, let's cheer ourselves up.
We can watch the clip of your Dad freezing up on the news again.
- Merry Christmas. - [Both laugh]