'Twas the night before Christmas!
And all through the park...
There are a bunch of people saying "hey, Johnny, why's that tree still dark?"
- Huh? - [Applause]
All right, folks. Well, before our big show-stopping solo,
Liv Rooney has the honor of lighting that tree.
So let's get her out here, huh? Come on.
[Cheering]
[Chuckles, clears throat]
Thank you, Johnny. Lighting this tree is a great honor...
But it is one that I would like to pass on to the young and...
Very talented Jenny Keene.
This is her moment.
[Applause]
Maybe all Jenny needed was that one person to truly care about her
so that she could blossom into the greatest version of herself.
Get off my stage, blondie.
[Giggles]
Okay. Maybe not.
Merry Christmas, Stevens Point.
[Cheering, exclaims]
Ha! Yes!
Ha ha.
Uh, Dad, is that supposed to be smoking like that?
Well, it looks like little Jenny Keene just ruined Christmas.
Christmas Tree down. Christmas Tree down!
Liv Rooney, you set me up!
She ruined my big moment.
I hate this town, and everyone in it!
And that, ladies and gentlemen...
Was little Jenny Keene's impression of Ebenezer Scrooge.
Yay, Jenny. [Chuckles]
Oh, what a talented little actress, am I right?
So that's probably it for the show.
Merry Christmas?
Oh. Wow.
She really is a monster.
Yeah, I told you, Mom. She is way worse than I was.
It's Christmas, Sweetie. Sure.
Well, I guess the show's over.
- It's a bummer. - Oh, I know, honey. I was...
I was really looking forward to your big solo.
Don't give up yet.
I think Dad and I may have actually found a way to save Christmas.
Get ready for "Christmas unplugged".
[Squeals]
And Liv gets to sing "let it snow".
That is the only song you'll be singing, right?
[Guitar playing]
Oh, the weather outside is frightful.
But the fire is so delightful.
And since we've no place to go...
Let it snow, let it snow. Let it snow.
[Flute playing]
Oh, it doesn't show signs of stopping.
And I've bought some corn for popping.
The lights are turned way down low.
Let it snow, let it snow. Let it snow...
Even though it didn't snow, it's kind of the perfect Christmas Eve, huh?
Yeah, except I already broke my helicopter.
Well, at least you have a backup.
Nope, broke that one too.
All the way home I'll be warm.
The fire is slowly dying.
And my dear, we're still goodbye-ing.
But as long as you love me so.
Let it snow, let it snow. Let it snow.
[Cheering]
All right, listen. Good night, everybody.
I know it didn't snow, but at least it didn't rain, right?
- [Thunder crashes] - [All groan]
Are you kidding me?