Hey, honey. Check out my latest innovation in tree decorating.
I built a base that turns the tree so you can decorate it easier.
I call it "The Tree-zy Susan".
Yep. After just three weeks in the wood shop,
Dad has shaved five minutes off our decorating time.
I finished my Christmas wish list, Mommy.
The trick to getting what you really want for Christmas
is to first ask for the impossible.
I throw in a "Mommy" or two to grease the wheels.
I only want one thing, Mommy.
Peace on earth, good will toward men.
[Sighs] Sorry, I guess that's two things.
Well, they're a little tough to wrap and put under the tree.
What else is on your list?
Well, I didn't think I'd need a backup, but I guess I could settle for...
The Screaming Dragon remote pilot helicopter
with a built-in 13-megapixel camera.
Well, they're kind of expensive.
But I think we can get you that helicopter.
That's how you get 'er done, son.
Oh, please. Letting Parker think he's "working us".
Has become a Christmas tradition.
Last year he asked us to fill in the hole in the ozone layer.
He got a bike.
Seriously? A helicopter?
He's just gonna break it in the first 15 minutes.
May as well flush your money down the toilet.
Oh, wait, you can't.
His remote control submarine already clogged it.
Mm, I hadn't thought about that.
Operation toilet dive was a search and rescue mission
for the action figure I flushed the day before.
Never leave a man behind.
Yeah, you're not helping your case here.
I hate to say it, but I think Joey's right.
You're just too young for such a sophisticated toy.
All I want for Christmas now is revenge.
And the helicopter.
And the peace on earth stuff, but mostly revenge.
Dad, come on. Joey's ruining Christmas.
Do something.
I'm a little tied up right now, buddy.