Boom!
That is 14 in a row.
Where's your defense, little man?
It is three feet below your shoulders, that's where.
How is this even fun for you?
I'm done here.
Oh, come on. One more?
I'm just trying to keep my mind off Maddie and the junior Olympics.
I really don't want her to leave.
Have you heard anything?
I keep my nose out of such affairs.
Come on. One more game?
Why don't you just get Joey to play with you?
He's not leaving for his pottery class for a little while.
Wait a minute... Pottery class?
He told me he was meeting with his zombie appreciation society.
Wait, he's lying to us?
Why would you lie about doing either of those things?
Unless you're doing something even more pathetic.
What do you think he's up to?
I don't know.
Just when you think you have a munch all figured out,
he throws you a curveball.
Maybe he has a secret girlfriend.
(Both laughing)
Okay, look... we need to figure out what Joey's hiding.
Last time he had a secret, I woke up with 64 white mice in my bed.
Wait, so are you saying this is an affair you would stick your nose in?
Ah, Diggie...
My nose goes where it's needed.