Thank you for watching my audition video.
I would love to be your Stephanie Einstein on "Sing it loud!"
(Laughing)
That was great, honey.
Now you go on up to bed and we will mail this out tomorrow.
Thanks Mom.
(Chuckles) Okay.
Sleep well, honey.
Hello Hollywood.
Hope you enjoyed Liv. She's adorable.
But while we have you here,
I'd like to throw my hat in the ring for Stephanie's mom, Alberta Einstein.
Now, I don't have a script, but here's how I imagine this character would be.
(Sighs)
(With British accent) Hello.
Well, I didn't see you there.
The name's Einstein. (Chuckles) Alberta Einstein.
Pete:  Hey, honey, You want some popcorn?
Yeah, sure. That'd be great.
Again, I hope you'll consider Karen Rooney for the role of Alberta Einstein.
Thanks.
(With British accent) Cheers.