(Gasps) Oh.
So how'd it go?
Did you make the team?
Well, they said she had a lot of potential.
And she was one of only three sophomores invited to try out.
Yeah, they... they said I did a really great job
and they said for me to keep practicing.
- Oh, Maddie. - I'm so sorry.
Yeah, because we start in ten weeks.
I made the team!
Bam! What?!
Did you see their faces?
I didn't give it away. I didn't give it away!
Oh, Maddie, I am so proud of you.
Thanks, mom.
Wow, I'm really going to miss you, Rooney.
But I'll be here waiting for you when you come back.
(Chuckles) Thanks, Diggie.
(Mockingly clears throat) No way.
Ahem!
So, um...
I could be gone for a really long time.
You just say the word...
Don't go! Forget your dreams.
What?
I'm totally kidding. You have to go.
I already made plans for your half of the room.