All righty.
You figured out my secret.
I'm in a drum circle.
We're called the bucketstreet boys.
Go ahead. Make fun.
Joey, that was awesome.
And you know I die a little inside every time I compliment you.
I was really impressed too, Joe.
Yeah, no one's taking you seriously right now, Diggie.
Stand down, soldier.
Stand down.
So what's with the sneaking around?
Well, you know, some of my guys are a little shy.
A lot shy.
So we've been rehearsing in private.
But we're going public tomorrow between fifth and sixth period.
Whoa... that's hallway rush hour.
That's the point.
We're gonna stop traffic with our insta-jam
and pick up some insta-hallway cred.
That's cool. I mean, you just became slightly less munchy.
I just don't get why you keep the one thing you do well a secret.
(Scoffs) One thing.
Clearly you have never seen me give medicine to a cat.