I am calm.
I am relaxed.
I am a happy tree.
(Thuds loudly)
You are making it very hard to be a happy tree!
Sorry, Liv, I'm just... I'm losing my mind
waiting for this letter that will tell me
if I made tryouts for the junior Olympics.
Junior Olympics.
It's just the chance to play basketball
for my country and travel the world for a year
and score a bangin' team usa duffel bag.
You know what... It's no big deal.
It's the biggest deal ever.
Bam. What?!
I just got home and now she might be leaving
for some once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
to represent our country as a junior olympian?
(Scoffs)
How selfish can she be?
Maddie, I totally hope you do get to do your basketball audition.
(Chuckles, snorts)
Okay, well, it's called a tryout.
Well, whatever it is called, I hope you break a leg.
(Laughs)
Maddie.
This was on the porch.
(Exclaims) My letter!
I'm going to throw up. Okay.
Okay... you open it.
Don't touch it! Okay.
Okay. Ready?
Socks?
"You have been pranked by Joey."
(Laughing)
Booyah!
(Chuckling) Should be booyah.