Maddie!
Look what just came. (Squeals)
It's your letter from the junior Olympics.
Oh, finally!
(Laughs)
Wait, this just got here?
It's midnight.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, it's this new feature that the post office has
where they wait until the last second
to deliver something important to build excitement.
It's called...
It's called "antici-post."
Liv...
When did this letter really get here?
Okay, so it got here this morning.
What?!
You had this all day?
Hey! You cannot blame the messenger.
Well, I can if the messenger never gave me the message.
Now, what is going on out here?
Liv hid my junior Olympics letter all day!
What?! Olivia Rooney.
Yeah, you see that... That is the face of an appalled mother.
You appalled her because you are appalling.
I wouldn't say mom looked appalled.
She just looks kind of worn out.
(Sputters)
Liv, you tried to sabotage me.
I would never sabotage your dream like that.
Well, now, Madison, that's not totally true.
Do you remember five years ago?
Liv's audition DVD?
We are not talking about five years ago, Karen.
No, I think I'd like to hear Karen's story.
Say goodbye to Hollywood, Liv.
Maddie, stop. What are you doing?
I'm destroying Liv's audition video.
I don't want her to leave.
Honey, no.
No, I know this is going to be hard, but this is Liv's dream.
We have to let her try.
If she doesn't, she will always wonder what might have happened.
You're right, mom.
I once passed up a chance to move to Indianapolis
to fill a coveted spot in a regional production of "Oliver"
as street urchin #3.
(With British accent) I carry that regret with me
every single day of me life.
You almost destroyed my audition DVD?
- Liv, I... - No, no.
Ha! It's cool.
Wow, for a while there, I thought I was the evil twin.
But it turns out we're both evil.
Samesies!
You can't call samesies.
I was like 10.
Okay.
I think we should focus less on the evil that you share and more on the love.
Neither one of you wanted the other one to leave.
(Sighs) Maddie, she's right.
I mean, I moved back to Wisconsin to be with you.
I'm not ready to let you go.
So yeah. I hid your letter.
I'm sorry.
Well, I mean...
I get it. Your heart was in the right place.
Liv, just know that whatever is in this letter...
We're never going to lose what we have.
That's right.
You'll always be sisters by chance, friends by choice.
Yeah, so let's not say that out loud anymore.
(Sighs) Open your letter.
Open the letter.
Diggie: Yeah, open the letter.
Okay, fine, I will...
Diggie?
What are you doing here?
Just walking by. Thought I'd say hello.
Oh. (Chuckles) Weird. But sweet.
All: Open the letter.
(Clears throat)
I made tryouts.
I made tryouts!
(Exclaiming)
This is huge.
I am so proud of you.
Wait, I have to be in Chicago for tryouts in six hours?
I'm never gonna make that.
Six hours?
Oh! Six hours.
What have I done? Okay.
Um, no no no. You know what?
I can help. I can have you packed in 5 1/2.
Whoo!
Huh.
This says tryouts are next weekend.
(Laughs, snorts)
I know.
Oh, but did you see her jump?
(Laughs) Maybe I am the evil twin.