Am I too late for the insta-jam?
I got a bathroom hall pass from my teacher,
but I didn't tell her what bathroom.
Guys, you made it.
By the time sixth period starts, you'll be able to say, "Joey Rooney...
I knew him when."
(Bell rings)
Attention, Ridgewood!
Get ready to get rhythm!
1, 2, 3, 4.
Really?
Seriously, now is not the time to be shy.
Oh, man, this is terrible.
We have to do something.
You're right.
I have an immobilizing dart gun in my pocket.
We can say he was dehydrated.
I think I have a better idea.
Thanks, man.
Now, are you guys drummers?
Or are you bummers?
Well, the joke is on you.
Because Joey's out there with the captain of the basketball team.
And you guys are just standing here, getting lectured by a fifth grader.
Hey, Joey, we got the band back together.
Oh ho ho!
All righty.
1, 2, 3, 4.
(Inaudible over drumming)
(Cheering)
- Way to go, Joey! - Not now, Diggie.
They love me.