I didn't open Maddie's letter,
but I struggled for hours about what to do with it.
In the end, I decided there really only was one right thing to do.
Hide it long enough for her to miss tryouts.
Yeah, it turns out that the toilet tank is not a great hiding place.
Mm, and...
There.
Oh, hair dryer.
Is there any problem you can't solve?
f-y-information, life is going to get a lot more complicated
for you both when you grow up.
(Knocking at door)
Karen: Liv, honey, can I come in?
Uh...
(Murmuring)
Okay, yeah. Come on in.
Hey.
How are you doing?
Oh! So good. I am phenomenal.
I am just great.
(Loud thuds)
(Sighs) Poor Maddie has been out on that basketball court all night.
She is so anxious waiting for this letter to arrive.
It's just cruel that they make her wait so long.
It is so cruel.
(Louder thuds)
(Sighs)
I have just been a nervous wreck thinking about another one of my babies
leaving the nest.
But you, you're right there.
Supporting your sister.
It's just like this picture you two made.
"Sisters by chance, friends by choice."
You know... you girls live that every day.
Every day?
Ha ha! Twice on Sundays.
Oh, I remember the night you were leaving for Hollywood.
(Sighing)
Mom, mom, guess what.
What is it, Maddie?
We played basketball at recess today and I was better than everyone.
Even the boys. Bam!
- What? - Bam!
What?
Ooh, I like that.
Bam! What?!
What is happening?
Joey, Parker just follows you around
because he worships the ground you walk on.
It is cute that he can't take his eyes off of you.
So that's why he poops with the door open.
He'll grow out of that.
Appreciate the offer.
What offer?
Bluetoothin', babe gotta bail, brah.
Okay, here's aunt Dina's number in case you need to get ahold of us in L.A.
Keep it someplace safe.
Got it.
There she is. Look out, Hollywood.
It is Liv Rooney.
I had the most amaze-a-licious idea.
Instead of saying the name of my show, I should always sing it.
Sing it loud!
That's gonna get old.
Gonna?
All right, everybody.
Time to take mom and Liv to the airport.
Wait. I need a twin moment.
Are they gonna hug or fight?
I never know.
Look, I could be gone for a long time.
You say the word and I won't leave.
You have to go, Liv.
I'm going to miss you.
But this is your dream.
Thanks. That means everything to me.
Now go out and show Hollywood how we do it in Stevens Point.
Bam! What?!
Yeah, don't do that.
(Both chuckle)
Wow. (Laughs)
Thank you, mom.
Really needed that reminder of how selfless my sister was.
I would be a monster not to do the same thing for her.
Oh, a hideous monster.